

OLEKSANDR UNTERVALD

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- +38093 060 22 46
- untervaldthebest@gmail.co
- Ukraine, Kiyv
- in www.linkedin.com/in/oleks andr-untervald
- @hunter999999
- f https://www.facebook.com/oleksandr.untervald
- https://github.com/Oleksan drUntervald
- https://untervald-frontend-cv.vercel.app/

SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS / SASS / TAILWINDCSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT / REDUX
- NEXT.JS
- VITE / GULP / WEBPUCK
- GIT / GITHUB
- FIGMA

LANGUAGES

- English (B1)
- Uktaine (native)

8

PROFILE

I am a passionate front-end developer with experience in building responsive and interactive websites. I am proficient in HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, and modern frameworks like React and Next.js. I focus on creating user-friendly interfaces and enhancing web performance. Currently, I am working on personal projects to further develop my skills and stay up-to-date with the latest web technologies.



WORK EXPERIENCE

PET PROJECTS

FRONT-END FIELD

 I am currently focusing on developing my skills through the creation of personal pet projects. These projects allow me to explore and implement various web technologies while enhancing my understanding of front-end development. You can check my pet projects here: UnterCV or on my GITHUB!

Frontend-developer & Media Buyer

2021/10 - 2022/09

2024 - PRESENT

company: Imonetizet

- Creation, deploy and service of landing pages using: HTML, CSS, JS.
- Setting up a redirect, working with servers and domains.
- Setting up the cloaca robot with Keitaro: creating streams, loading Black/White pages, PostBack. Was responsible for proxy procurement.



EDUCATION

GENERAL EDUCATION

2016 Kyiv "University of Modern Knowledge"
Department of Law

IT EDUCATION

Esfirum IT School Frontend

2021 - 2022

2024 - in the process

Okten SCHOOL

School of business | Wardiere University